It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
Family Guy 10x20
Leggo My Meg-O
放开我的梅格
片名恶搞了Eggo华夫饼的广告语L'eggo my Eggo
另本集内容大量来自于《飓风营救》
好了 姑娘们
All right, ladies,
咱们分队开始躲避球吧
let's pick teams for dodgeball.
Connie 你愿意做队长么
Connie, would you like to be a captain?
当然
Sure.
我选除了Meg的所有人
I pick everyone except Meg.
选得好 开始
Fair enough. Go!
嘿 你们要去哪儿
Hey, where's everybody going?
我们可不是这样下课的噢
That's not how we end this class.
今天干得很好
Good job today.
上课表现得不错
Great class.
推得漂亮
Nice hustle.
嘿 你体育课上的怎样
Hey, how was gym class?
烂透了
Terrible.
知道么 我想我不能
You know, I don't think I can take
再忍受一个学期了 Ruth
another semester at this school, Ruth.
太痛苦了
It's torture.
比在飞机上坐婴儿旁边还要痛苦
It's worse than sitting next to a baby on an airplane.
什么风把你吹到肯塔基州来的
So what brings you to Kentucky?
我是来看望家人的
I'm visiting my family.
啊 居家男人
Ah, family man.
我么 单身但准备结婚了
Me? Single and ready to mingle.
Tom Brunell是我的名字 保险是我的干活
Tom Brunell's the name. Insurance is the game.
而且现在 这份工作可是很眷顾我哦
And right now, the game is very good to me.
嘿 我想到了
Hey, I know!
如果你这么讨厌在这的话
If you hate it so much here,
你为什么不去巴黎
why don't you come to Paris
我和一起待一个学期呢
for a semester with me instead?
我下周就出发
I'm leaving next week.
你要去巴黎一个学期?
You're going to Paris for a semester?
是啊 这是高中办的一个项目
Yeah, it's a program sponsored by the high school.
而且我姑姑在那里还有间公寓
My aunt even has an apartment there
我们可以免费住在那
that we can stay in for free.
天啊 听上去太棒了
Oh, my God, that sounds so amazing!
打扰了 我想问你
Excuse me, I was wondering
是否愿意周五和我去跳舞呢
if you would go to the dance with me on Friday.
Chris 是我 Meg
Chris, it's me, Meg.
好吧 那么没人愿意了
Well, that's everybody.
现在我们继续播放《埃塞俄比亚囤积者》
TV ANNOUNCER: We now return to Ethiopian Hoarders.
我不知道事情是怎么发展成这样的
I don't know how it got like this!
爸 妈
Dad, Mom,
我有些事要问你们一下
there's something I want to ask you.
我能去巴黎留学一个学期么
Can I go to school in Paris for a semester?
什么? 巴黎?
What? Paris?
嘿 我在巴黎有个笔友
Hey, you know, I have a pen pal in Paris.
你能帮我把这封信交给他么
Would you mind bringing him this letter?
我们正在吵架呢
We're fighting.
Meg 我们很愿意送你去巴黎学习一学期
Meg, I'd love to send you to Paris for a semester,
但我们负担不起啊
but we can't afford that.
但我可以自己出钱
But I can pay for it myself.
我所有的兼职工钱都存下来了
I've been saving up from all my part-time jobs.
你挺聪明嘛 Meg
That's smart of you, Meg.
有时有我也
You know, sometimes I do
做点兼职赚个闲钱
part-time jobs for extra cash.
给我钱 给我钱
Gimme money. Gimme money.
小心一点儿 宝贝
You be careful, sweetie,
飞机一降落你就给我们打电话
and call us as soon as the plane lands.
好的 妈 我会的
Okay, Mom, I will.
我会想你的 爸
I'll miss you, Dad.
我一直不擅长说再进(再见)
I've never been very good at saying good-bee.
再进了 Meg
Good-bee, Meg.
我回来会给你带
And I'm gonna bring you back
特别的礼物哟 小伙计
something special, little guy.
别管我了 你自己能找到个人上床就行了
Don't worry about me. Just get yourself laid.
你能帮我弄到French Stewart的签名么
Will you get me French Stewart's autograph?
美演员 出演过《歪星撞地球》中的Harry
他只是名字是French(法国人)而已
代我向巴黎的新桥问好
Say hello to the Pont Neuf for me,
或者用我喜欢名字来叫它 我的灵感之地…
or as I like to call it, my inspiration point...
哦 你已经走了
Oh, you're gone.
一家人也走了
And the family's gone.
天呐 我们真的在巴黎耶
Oh, my God, we're actually here in Paris.
这太令人激动了
This is so exciting!
日安 外国人
Good day, foreigners.
代表法国 我们对你们投降了
On behalf of the country of France, we surrender.
天啊 我喜欢你的气息
Oh, my God, I love your breath.
嗨 我是Meg
Hi, I'm Meg.
这是我朋友 Ruth
This is my friend, Ruth.
你们想要一起搭计程车么
Would you ladies like to share a cab,
或者用我们的说法 "搭儿计程车儿"
Or as we say,"sharre a cabbuh"?
好呀
Sure.
听起来好极了
That sounds great.
噢 请不要怀疑
Oh, and please do not be suspicious
我在机场
that I am at the airport
却什么行李也没有
with no baggage whatsoever.
用法式口音念一个名字特带劲儿
A cool name to say with a French accent
就是 爱死蹲 裤衩儿(阿什顿库彻)
is Ashtahn Kootchere.
再见
Bye!
谢啦
Thanks!
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
我给你弄到点儿新鲜货
I've got some fresh arrivals for you.
什么样的
How are they?
如果按十分制的话
On a scale from un to dix,
她们大概是三分黑木耳
they're about a trois.
哇 这地方太赞了
Wow, this place is awesome!
是呀
I know!
嘿 你想对着劲爆的音乐像2B一样跳舞么
Hey, you wanna dance around like morons to loud music?
我待会回来
I'll be right back.
我还在美国的时候就憋着泡屎了
I've been holding in a dump since America.
Griffin家
Griffin residence.
嗨 爸 是我
Hi, Dad, it's me.
只是想告诉你们我安全抵达
Just wanted you to know I got here safe.
而且无恙?
And sound?
是的 爸 而且无恙
Yes, Dad, and sound.
噢 好的
(relieved):Oh, good.
"无恙"才是我关心的
The "sound" is what concerns me.
噢 这里太棒了 爸 - 嗯
- Oh, it's so amazing here, Dad. - Yep.
- 你真应该来瞧瞧 - 嗯哼
- You should see it. - Uh-huh.
- 我们住的公寓特别大 - 嗯哼
- The apartment we're staying in is huge, - Uh-huh.
- 然后还有很棒的视野 可以看到… - 嗯哼
- and has an incredible view of... - Uh-huh.
Peter在S06E04也对Meg做过同样的事
爸 出了点事
Dad, something's going on.
有人闯进来了
Some men just broke in.
天啊 他们抓了Ruth
Oh, my God! They've got Ruth!
现在 我觉得他们要来抓我了
And now, I think they're coming after me!
好了 Meg
All right, Meg,
我需要你仔细听好:
I need you to listen to me very carefully:
惊慌
panic.
这和《飓风营救》里的台词正好相反
不要关注任何细节
Pay no attention to detail.
放开你思维的束缚
Let your mind race.
短暂 急促的呼吸
Take short, rapid breaths.
然后藏到床下
Then hide under the bed,
但把你的双脚伸到外面
but leave two of your feet sticking out.
天啊 爸
Oh, my God, Dad!
他们会抓走我吗 我好害怕
Are they gonna take me? I'm so scared!
Meg? Meg?
我不知道你是谁 我也不知道你的目的是什么
I don't know who you are.I don't know what you want.
但我什么能力也没有
But I have a very particular lack of skills.
我永远不会找到你
I will never be able to find you,
但我有的是 2美元
but what I do have is two dollars
还有一只卡西欧腕表
and a Casio wristwatch.
你可以得到其中之一
You can have one of them.
黑色达卡
Drakkar Noir.
一款男士香水
这些家伙是来真的
These guys are serious.
Lois Meg死翘翘了
Lois, Meg's dead!
求你们了 你们肯定能做点什么
Please, there's gotta be something you can do!
我女儿现在处境非常危险啊
My little girl is in terrible danger!
女士 带走你女儿的人
Ma'am, the men who took your daughter
很有可能是
are most likely members
来自一个经营多年的人贩子团伙
of a sophisticated network of human smugglers.
如果没有在96小时内找到她
If she's not found within 96 hours,
那她就永远也找不到了
chances are she's gone forever.
那我们得抓紧了
Then we've gotta hurry!
抱歉 我们不能开始搜索
Sorry, we can't begin our search
直到她失踪96小时了才行
until she's been missing for 96 hours.
天啊 我的儿啊
Oh, my God! My baby!
是的 那里可是有非常恐怖的性交易呢
Yeah, there's a pretty grisly sex trade over there.
一般情况 我们最后只能埋葬他们的肖像了
Usually we just end up burying framed pictures.
噢 Peter 这就是场噩梦啊
Oh, Peter! This is a nightmare!
下面情况怎样
What's going on down there?
他们会找到她么
Are they gonna find her?
情况不是很妙
Doesn't look good.
Stewie 我想我们只有一个方法
Stewie, I think there's only one way
才能再见到Meg了
we're ever gonna see Meg again.
我们俩必须亲自处理这事儿了
You and I have to take matters into our own hands.
什么 你什么意思
What? What are you talking about?
听着 你是唯一一个掌握
Look, you're the only one who's got the know-how
能找到她能力和技术的
and the technology to help us track her down.
哼 这就怪了
Hmm. Interesting.
上周 我的小玩意儿还叫"废物"来着
Last week, all my gadgets were "hooey,"
我想你就是这么说的
I think was the word.
- 我没有说… - 你说了"废物"
- I didn't say... - You said "hooey"!
好了 我已经给咱俩订好了飞机
All right, I've booked us on a flight
还有2小时起飞
that leaves in two hours,
那么 呃 我应该刷谁的信用卡
so, um, whose credit card shall we put it on?
就刷你的吧 我会还你的
Just put it on yours and I'll pay you back.
呃 我怎么感觉一般这种情况
Yeah, I feel like when that happens,
我的钱都要不回来了
I sometimes don't get paid back.
Brian借钱从来不还 见S04E20
比如什么时候
Like when?
《泽西男孩》音乐剧 莫顿牛排馆 快活林赌场
Jersey Boys, Morton's Steakhouse, Foxwoods...
快活林赌场在康涅狄格州 是世界上最大的赌场之一
快活林赌场和《泽西男孩》那是同一次旅行里的
Foxwoods and Jersey Boys was the same trip!
既然这样 那好吧
You know what? Fine.
我-我还是刷我的卡
I'll-I'll put it on my card,
但 我-我要强调这是个礼物
but I-I-I'm just gonna say it's a gift
因为只有这样我才会继续替你付钱
because that's the only way I can do this anymore.
好了 我们着陆后的首要任务
All right, the first thing we've got to do when we land
是去看看Meg被绑架的公寓
is check the apartment where Meg was abducted
看能不能发现点线索
and see if we can find some clues.
听起来不错 我刚就这么想来着
That sounds good. That's what I was thinking.
打扰一下 我们能否换下座位
Excuse me, do you mind if we switch seats
这样我们一家人就能坐到一起了
so my family can sit all together?
不 我们…我们不换
No, we don't... we-we don't switch.
因为我们订票的时候
'Cause when we booked,
他们没有3个连在一起…
they didn't have three together...
女士 女士 你的规划不善
Ma'am, ma'am, your poor planning
对我来说又不是什么紧急事件
does not constitute an emergency for me.
你们会在巴黎再见的 去坐下吧
You'll see him in Paris. Go sit down.
天 绑架Meg的人现在可能在法国的任何一个角落
God, Meg's kidnappers could be anywhere in France by now.
但我们有一条线索 Brian
Well, we do have one lead, Brian.
我录到了那个绑架者的声音
I have a recording of the kidnapper's voice.
什么 你有? 怎么来的
What? You do? How?
我录下了那个绑架者
I recorded the kidnapper's phone call
和胖子的通话
with the fat man.
其实 Brian 我录下了
You see, Brian, I record
所有打进或打出我们家的电话
all phone calls coming in or out of the house.
你-你-你录了?
Y-Y-You do?
是啊 其中有我最爱的一通
Yep. This one's one of my faves.
你好 这里是基本业务部 你有什么需要
WOMAN: Hello, Fundamental Industries. How can I help you?
嗯 呃 这…这里是"啪啪啪"兄弟公司么
BRIAN: Yeah, um, is this... is this Bang Brothers?
是的
WOMAN:Yes.
噢 好 我-我想取消我的订阅
BRIAN: Oh. Okay. I-I-I'd like to cancel my subscription.
呃 你的名字是?
WOMAN:Uh, what's your name?
BRIAN:Brian Griffin.
那你是订的哪个网站的片子
WOMAN: And which site did you belong to?
呃 "插入船长"
BRIAN:Uh... Captain Stabbin'.
据说确实有这个网站
怎么写的
WOMAN:And how are you spelling that?
呃 "船长"两个字
BRIAN:Uh... uh, "Captain", full word,
然后"插撸" 提手旁 一个千 一个臼 然后一个提手一个鲁
then "Stabbin',"S-T-A-B-B-I-N apostrophe.
好的 我查一下
WOMAN:Okay, I'm checking.
那个 还是换成"插入"吧
BRIAN: You know, in-instead of a "G" at the end.
抱歉 先生 我没有找到你说的片子的网站
WOMAN: I'm sorry, sir.I'm not finding that site.
请问一下题材是什么
Uh, what was the subject matter?
呃 一个人在船上干小妞
BRIAN: Um... a guy doing chicks on a boat
戴着 呃 船长的帽子
in a, uh, captain's hat.
好 我查一下
WOMAN: Okay, I'm checking.
那个 呃
BRIAN: The, um...
那个 乘客刚 呃 刚刚登记好
the, passengers had, uh, just signed up
要在海湾来一次旅行
for a tour of the harbor
然后剩下的事就发生了
and then all that stuff happened.
好吧 你已经表达得很明白了
Okay, you made your point.
好了 这就是Meg待的地方
Well, this is where Meg was staying.
噢 我以为巴黎会更诗情画意一点
Oh. I thought Paris would be a bit more picturesque.
而不是交通拥堵
Instead it's just traffic
还有个壮汉在使用千斤顶
and some big guy using a jackhammer.
但是先森 介可不系千斤顶哦
But monsieur, ziss is not a jackhammer.
这是"青筋顶"
It is a "Jacqueshammer."
jacques相当于英语中的jack
天 比我想象的还糟
Oh, God, it's worse than I imagined.
对了 也许
You know, maybe it'd help
你查一下Meg到巴黎以后的
if we just tried to track Meg's movements
动向也许会有帮助
from the moment she arrived in France.
好主意 Brian
That's a good idea, Brian.
我们来试试谷歌地球
Let's try Google Earth.
值得一试
Worth a shot.
那里 放大
There. Enhance.
哇 我从来不知道电脑还能这么用
Wow, I never knew you could do this on a computer.
当然不了 你把所有在电脑上的时间
'Course not, you spend all your time on this
都用来看插入船长了
watching Captain Stabbin'.
好吧 我们得找到这个人
All right, we've got to find this man.
让我看看 这是在机场照的
Let's see, this was taken at the airport.
他可能是个打前站的
He could be some sort of lookout
专挑那些刚下飞机的妹子
who spots girls fresh off the plane.
嗯 你应该是对的 Brian 真是个败类
Yes, you're probably right, Brian. Such scum.
我敢打赌他们瞄准了年轻女孩
I'll bet they target young girls
就跟陆军广告瞄准了那些少数族裔一样
the way Army commercials target minorities.
嘿 其他的黑哥们
Hey. Other black guys.
没那么糟 对吧
It ain't so bad.
天啊 Stewie 他在那
Oh, my God, Stewie! There he is!
嘿 兄弟 我们有些问题想问问你
Hey, buddy, we've got a few questions for you!
不好意思 但这里是"吸烟者专区"
Excuse me, but this is a "smoking only" area.
噢 抱歉 那你有 呃…
Oh, sorry. Do you have a, uh...
知道么 我仅当喝酒的时候才会抽烟
You know, I really only smoke when I drink.
噢 这真好
Oh. Well, this is nice.
这样方式干这个还真不错
This is a nice way to do this.
听着 我们想知道: 你见过这女孩么
Look, we need to know:have you seen this girl?
快 他要逃掉了
Quick! He's getting away!
噢 不 他是那种会跑酷的家伙
Oh, no, he's one of those parkour, free-running guys.
跑酷起源于法国 有经典跑酷电影《暴力13街区》
我们永远抓不到他了
We'll never catch him!
噢 不 我之前喝得太醉了
Oh, no. I have chateau'ed myself.
妈的 他还没告诉我们什么就死掉了
Damn it. He died before he could tell us anything.
Brian 他才是第一个人
Brian, he's the first guy.
第一个人一般都会死掉的
The first guy always dies.
但我肯定他不是一个人在战斗
Well, I'm sure he didn't work alone.
也许这里能找到点有用的东西
Maybe there's something in here we can use.
呃 这家伙用魔术贴钱包
Ugh, this guy has a Velcro wallet.
成熟点吧
Grow up.
好了 这就是他钱包里的地址
All right, this is the address that was in his wallet.
但我们怎么确定
Yeah, but how are we gonna know for sure
是否是他们绑架了Meg呢
if these are the guys who took Meg?
我们有绑架者声音的录音 记得么
Well, we have the kidnapper's voice on tape, remember?
黑色达卡
Drakkar Noir.
我可以用这里面的语音识别软件
I can use the voice recognition software
来确认声音是否吻合
in this recorder to confirm a match.
现在 给
Now, here.
拿着这个公文包
Take this briefcase.
我们现在是东欧古龙水推销员
We're Eastern European cologne salesmen.
我们问他们想要什么
We ask them what they want,
当他们说要"黑色达卡"时--
and when they say "Drakkar Noir"--
而且他们都会说--
which they all will--
我们就能知道是否找对人了
we'll know if we have our man.
卖黑色达卡的?
Drakkar Noir?
好了 虽然这不是他
All right, well, that's not him,
但这一定会很容易的
but this is gonna be easy.
好了 先生们 既然你们都已经闻过
Well, gentlemen, now that you have smelled
我们的古龙水了 最想要哪一款呢
all of our colognes, what'll it be?
我要黑色达卡
I will take some Drakkar Noir.
那你呢
How 'bout you?
我身上很臭
I am disgusting,
所以我要2瓶黑色达卡
so I will take two bottle Drakkar Noir.
那你呢 这位老大
How 'bout you, chief?
嗯
Hmm.
让我先快速长出胡子再想想看
Let me quickly grow beard and think about it.
我要黑色达卡
I will take Drakkar Noir.
你TM的搞毛线啊
What the hell are you doing?!
我们在飞机上就没吃过东西了
We haven't eaten since the plane.
我饿屎了
I'm starving.
这女孩在哪
Where is this girl?
她在哪
Where is she?!
我们把女孩都关在楼上
We keep girls upstairs.
我希望你下地狱被火烧
I hope you burn in hell along with the guy
跟那个想出给火鸡填料的家伙一起
who came up with stuffing a turkey.
嘿
Hey!
谁想来点我的"屁眼儿面包"
Who wants to try some of my "Butthole Bread"?
Meg?
救…我
Help... me.
噢 我们是来这儿救其他人的 宝贝
Oh, we're here to help somebody else, sweetheart.
走 走 走 快走 别…别看她
Go, go, go, go. Don't... Don't look at her.
别看她 这是我的错
Don't look at her. That was my mistake.
Stewie 到处都没看到Meg
Stewie, I don't see Meg anywhere.
Brian 看
Brian, look!
上帝啊
Oh, my God!
Meg!
怎么个情况?
What the hell?
你那帽子哪来的
Where'd you get that hat?
呃 一个女孩给我的
Uh, a girl gave it to me.
那她长什么样
Well, what did she look like?
她人非常好(潜台词长的丑)
She had a great personality.
那就是她
That's her.
她在哪 在这里吗
Where is she? Is she here?
不 呃 他们刚刚把她带走
No, uh, they took her just a little while ago.
每周三晚上
Every Wednesday night,
他们都会拍卖掉一些女孩
they auction some of the girls off.
周三
Wednesday?
真是个奇怪的晚上
What a weird night
来拍卖女孩给人当奴隶
to auction girls off into slavery.
呃 其实 周末
Well, you know, on the weekend,
人们可能都有安排了
people probably have plans.
有安排?
Have plans?
还有什么事比
What are you doing that's more important
买卖人更重要
than buying somebody?
听我说 那个地方在哪
Look, where is this place?
他们在哪拍卖
Where do they have the auction?
我不知道
I don't know,
但是这有一路免费班车
but there is a courtesy shuttle
每20分钟一趟
that runs every 20 minutes.
什么
What?
性奴拍卖
啊 妈的 我们刚好错过一辆
Aw, damn it. We just missed it.
还有20分钟你准备干嘛
What do you wanna do for 20 minutes?
呃 我不知道你怎么样
Well, I don't know 'bout you,
但我准备练练身体
but I'm gonna work out.
这样你才能保持身体有型
That's how you stay in shape.
只要有空就抽出来练
You just fit it in when you have free time,
随时随地不管你在哪里
wherever you are,wherever you can.
这地板上有精液
There's semen on this floor.
Stewie 快看
Stewie, look!
我们得进去
We gotta get in there!
嘿 这还有一个
Hey, got one more here!
噢 我们这是在哪
Oh, where are we?
我来自亚特兰大
I'm from Atlanta.
我都不知道我们在哪了
I don't know where we are!
嘿 你们最好快点 他们马上要开始了
Hey, you better hurry. They're starting soon.
你知道棘手的地方是什么吗
You know what's messed up?
这一切都是为了慈善事业
This is all for charity.
所有的收益都会进入牛津饥荒救济委员会
All the proceeds are going to Oxfam.
我希望我们来的还不是太晚
I hope we're not too late.
你不应该在外面瞎逛的
You should not be out here.
- 马上开始竞标了 - 搞毛呢
- Bidding is about to start. - What the hell?
Stewie!
目前的出价是20万美刀
FEMALE AUCTIONEER:The current bid is $200,000.
天啊
Oh, my God.
一次 二次
AUCTIONEER:Going once, twice...
20万美刀成交
Sold for $200,000.
记住
Remember:
使用visa金卡可以有现金返还噢
There is cash back when you use your Visa Gold.
我们的下一件拍卖品是刚刚到的
Our next item appears to be a late entry.
还不在目录里面
It is not in the catalog.
见鬼了
BRIAN:What the hell?
好了 诸位 调亮点灯光
All right, fellas, bring the lights up a bit,
放我给你的CD 然后我们开始吧
play the CD I gave you and let's do this!
(水果姐的加州女孩)
啊 这就对了 你喜欢么
Ah, that's right. You like that?
有人出价5万
I have $50,000.
有人出价7万5
I have $75,000.
谢谢你 Brett Ratner
Thank you, Brett Ratner.
美电影导演 MV导演
他给水果姐拍过I Kissed A Girl的MV 这首不是他拍的
有人出10万?
Do I have $100,000?
- 噢 上帝 - 50万
- Oh, for God's sake. - $500,000.
有人出价50万
We have $500,000.
50万一次 50万两次
Going once, going twice,
成交
sold...
给那个不怎么来拍卖的先生
to the man who doesn't quite get auctions.
真好玩
That was so fun.
你准备怎么付钱
How do you be paying?
噢 我 呃 我没有钱
Oh, I, uh, I don't have any money.
我们能不能再商量商量
Can we work it out,
呃 也许用点…别的方式
uh, maybe, some... other way?
等一下
Wait a minute.
气味怎么感觉没那么难闻啊
Something doesn't smell funny here.
你不是阿拉伯人
You're not Arab!
你们两个跟我走
You two are coming with me.
下面一个女孩非常完美
AUCTIONEER:This next girl is perfect
但是 是对于那些想买一个性奴
for those of you who want to buy a sex slave
又不想花那么多钱的
but don't want to spend sex-slave money.
天啊 是Meg
Oh, my God, Meg!
不知道他们会给她放什么音乐
Wonder what music they're gonna use for her?
(游戏节目"Let's Make A Deal"中的经典音乐)
嗯 挺合适的
Huh, seems about right.
妈的 我们本来离救到Meg就差一步了
Damn it. We were so close to saving Meg.
嘿 我的姐姐在哪
Hey, where's my sister?
她大概正在享用"烤肉串"了 用我们的话来说
She's probably having her shish kababbed as we speak.
指男人的那话儿
我是从《欲望都市2》中Samantha那听来的
I heard that from Samantha in Sex and the City 2.
阿-我不要听-我不要听 我还没看呢
Ah-ba-ba-ba-ba, I haven't seen it yet.
这和剧情无关的
That doesn't hurt the story.
那么现在准备受…
And now prepare to...
我们有间牢房的
We have a jail cell.
我老是跟他们说
I always tell them,
"把囚犯关进牢房"
"Put the prisoners in the jail cell,"
但他们总说"还是直接用链子把它们锁在管子上吧"
but they always say,"Just chain 'em up to a pipe."
全是二货
Idiots.
嘿 刚才合作不错哟 Brian
Hey, that was some good teamwork, Brian.
但我们以前就像Lewis和Clark
We were like Lewis and Clark
在S08E07中也出现过这两人的段子
这两人为美国历史上著名探险家
还有那个喜欢弄翻独木舟的小子
and the guy who likes to tip over canoes.
啊 这些湍流很危险
Ugh, these rapids are treacherous.
我们得在夜幕降临前划到平静的水域
We should reach calmer waters by nightfall.
啊噢 地震啦
Uh-oh!Earthquake!
嘿 快停下
Hey, come on!
小心点
Careful!
妈的 他怎么还和我们在一起
Damn it. Why is he still with us?
可不是嘛
I know!
直到现在 徒步穿越
Until now, walking to the other end
美国还是个很吃香的工作呢
of the United States seemed like such a good job.
她在那 快
There she is! Hurry!
Stewie 你要干嘛
Stewie, what are you doing?
我们用脚的话是绝对追不上飞车的
We'll never catch a speeding car on foot.
你从来没看过动作片么
Haven't you ever seen an action movie?
我们只需
All we have to do
对角穿过邻近的场地就可以了
is cut diagonally across any nearby field.
看到没
See?
啊 日了 他们把她带上游艇了
Aw, crap, they're taking her onto that yacht.
好吧 我们只要追上游艇就可以了
All right, we just gotta catch up to the boat.
那我们要怎么才能办到呢
Well, how we gonna do that?
噢 酷啊 这车有追车GPS系统
Oh, cool! They got Car Chase GPS.
惊险的回到车流当中
FEMALE GPS VOICE:Back up dangerously into traffic.
继续在繁忙的反向车道上往前开500米
Proceed wrong way down busy street for 500 meters.
说"抓紧" 然后开下阶梯
Say "hang on" and drive down staircase.
抓紧
Hang on!
出现明显的有特技人员的穿帮镜头
Poorly edited shot where driver is obviously stuntperson.
像个混蛋一样在封闭的车内留了个屁
Leave fart in closed car like a dick.
不好意思啦
BRIAN:Sorry about that!
好了 他们应该是把她抓到下层甲板了
All right, they're probably holding her below deck.
你去右边 我去左边
You take the right side. I'll take the left.
你会需要这个的
You're gonna need this.
什么 我-我从来没杀过人呢
What? I-I-I've never killed anybody before.
在912中杀过Stewie
放轻松 他们是阿拉伯人
Relax, they're Arabs.
人们依然会为你欢呼的
People will still be rooting for you.
嘿
Hey!
妈了个巴子的
Son of a bitch.
噢 这就和电子游戏一样
Oh. This is like a video game.
啊 看来我很擅长这个嘛
Ah, I'm kinda good at this.
别了 笨蛋
Later, dink.
这一枪是还给你们的
That's for shooting one of our guys!
整到你了吧 射你一脸
We got you! In your face!
我们的船赢了 我们的船
Our boat! Our boat!
这艘船
This boat!
放开我 你这死肥子
Let me go, you fat bastard!
我绝不会给你当性奴的
I will never be your sex slave!
你理解错了
You misunderstand.
我不是买你来当奴隶的
I did not buy you to be my slave.
我是为我儿买的 但也不是做他的奴隶
I bought you for my son, and not to be his slave,
而是他的妻子
but to be his wife.
妻子?
Wife?
Faisal!
这是Faisal
This is Faisal,
我的儿子 也是我王位的继承人
my son and the heir to my throne.
我父亲说的没错
My father was correct.
你的美貌难以言表
Your beauty knows no bounds.
美丽的女神 我希望
Fair goddess, it is my hope
你会同意做我的妻子
that you will agree to be my wife,
但选择权在你手上
but the choice is yours.
如果你说"不"
If you say "no,"
我会护送你飞回家人身边
I will have you flown back to your family
用我的私人专机
on our private jet.
如果你说"是"
But if you say "yes,"
我就会用我的余生
I will spend the rest of my days
来实现你的每个愿望
making your every wish come true.
你愿意做我的妻子么 Meg公主
Will you be my wife, Princess Meg?
噢 我愿意 愿意
Oh, yes! Yes!
不
Nooooo!
Stewie?
嗨 Meg
Hi, Meg.
《黑衣人》中的记忆消除器
噢 甜心 真高兴你回来了
Oh honey, we are so glad to have you back
但你真的一点也不记得了么
but you really don't remember anything?
不完全是 妈
Not really, Mom.
我是说 一分钟前 我还被一个
I mean, one minute, I was being proposed to
帅气的阿拉伯王子求婚
by a handsome Arabian prince,
然后我只知道
and the next thing I know,
我在一家法国医院醒来了
I'm waking up in a French hospital.
噢 我们从Ruth的家长那听说了
Oh, and we heard from Ruth's parents.
她的舌头被拔了
She had her tongue ripped out.
还好我们没怎么受折磨 不是么
I guess we got off easy, huh?
对了 我们把你的所有邮件
Well, we put all your mail
都放到你房间的桌上了 甜心
on the desk in your room, sweetheart.
谢了 爸
Thanks, Dad.
我骗你的啦 你一封信也没有
I'm kidding. You didn't get any mail.